[
  {
    "id": 0,
    "question": "Which of the following is not a criterion for congruence of triangles?",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "option": "Side, Side, Side (SSS)"
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "option": "Angle, Angle, Angle (AAA)"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "option": "Side, Angle, Side (SAS)"
      }
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "Angle, Angle, Angle (AAA)"
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What is the third angle for the triangle where angle1 = 45° and angle2 = 45°?",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "option": "45°"
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "option": "90°"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "option": "60°"
      }
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "90°"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What is the third angle for the triangle where angle1 = 90° and angle2 = 60°?",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "option": "acute angle"
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "option": "obtuse angle"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "option": "right angle"
      }
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "acute angle"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "Which of the following can form a right angled triangle?",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "option": "1, 2, 3"
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "option": "3, 4, 5"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "option": "5, 6, 7"
      }
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3, 4, 5"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "Which of the following triangles are always similar?",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "option": "scalene triangle"
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "option": "isosceles triangle"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "option": "equilateral triangle"
      }
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "equilateral triangle"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "If one angle of a triangle is obtuse, then which one of the following is the possible measure of remaining angles?",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "option": "100°"
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "option": "90°"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "option": "85°"
      }
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "85°"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "The perimeter of scalene triangle with sides a, b, c is",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "option": "a + b + c"
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "option": "2a"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "option": "(a + b + c) / 2"
      }
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "a + b + c"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "A scalene triangle has ___ lines of symmetry",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "option": "no"
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "option": "100"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "option": "12"
      }
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "no"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "There is a right triangle PQR where: ∠ Q = 90°; ∠ P = ∠ R. What is the measure of ∠s P and R?",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "option": "45°"
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "option": "90°"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "option": "60°"
      }
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "45°"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What is the third angle for the triangle where angle1 = 45° and angle2 = 45°?",
    "options": [
      {
        "id": 0,
        "option": "acute angle"
      },
      {
        "id": 1,
        "option": "obtuse angle"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "option": "right angle"
      }
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "right angle"
  }
]
